{
    "question": "Di suruh     mengubah kalimat berikut ke dalam bentuk pasif mereka\r\n\r\n soalnya\" it is dais that many people are homeless after floods\"\r\npeople say that arthur is very rich",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "it is dais were\u00a0nomeless after floods by many people dan People was say athur is very rich.<br><br>Sorry if im wrong ty:)x",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "change-into-the-correct-simple-present-or-simple-past-form-1-i-897",
            "question": "change into the correct simple present or simple past form 1. I.....(live) right off an alleyway blablabla.. 2. It....(be) the alleyway behind blabla.. 3. this....(need) to be paid attention immediately and 4. ...... (require)immediate repairing. 5. blabla.. last night it ..... (rain) for maybe an hour, and look what it 6. ...... (do). 7. some of the potholes ..... (be) 5 inches deep. 8. please I .... (beg) you, blabla.. 9. we .... (need) the road resurfaced.\u00a0 10. it....(look) like a thrid world country outside my house. \u00a0 \u00a0 1. every day I .... (pass) rotan street to go to my office which it situated on burton street and 2. ..... (return) home the same route. this has been a routin for twelve years. but last week, to my dismay, I 3. .... (have) to go around to the other way when I 4. ...(return) home from my office. as I was going to turn to Rotan street, there 15. .... (be) a sign that all street users to rotan sreet 16. ... (can) enter it that day because one of the residentswas having a weeding party. 17. .... (have) to turn my car to pasadena street and I was trapped in a trafic jam half an hour. it 18. .... (be) a nuisance. I ..... (reach) home late in the evening. I think that streets 20..... (be) \u00a0for public use. it should not be use for private use. if you 21. ....(hold) a weeding party, you should rent a weeding hall or a meeting hall in the near sub district. streets 22 .... (be) for trafic, it \u00a023. .... (be) not for private party.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. lived<br>2.was<br>3.needed<br>4.required<br>5.rained<br>6.did<br>7.were<br>8.begged<br>9.needed<br>10.looked",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\n                change into the correct simple present or simple past form\n1.\n                <span>change into the correct simple present or simple past form\n<br>1. I..LIVE...(live) right off an alleyway blablabla..\n<br>2. It...IS...(be) the alleyway behind blabla..\n<br>3. this..NEEDS..(need) to be paid attention immediately and <br>4. ..REQUIRES.... (require)immediate repairing.\n<br>5. blabla.. last night it ..RAINED... (rain) for maybe an hour, and look what it <br>6. ...DOES... (do).\n<br>7. some of the potholes ..ARE... (be) 5 inches deep.\n<br>8. please I .BEG... (beg) you, blabla..\n<br>9. we ..NEED.. (need) the road resurfaced.\u00a0\n<br>10. it..LOOKS..(look) like a thrid world country outside my house.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0\n<span><br><br>1. every day I ..PASS.. (pass) rotan street to go to my office which it \nsituated on burton street and 2. .RETURN.... (return) home the same route. \nthis has been a routin for twelve years. but last week, to my dismay, I \n3. HAD.... (have) to go around to the other way when I 4. .RETURNED..(return) home \nfrom my office. as I was going to turn to Rotan street, there 15. .WAS... \n(be) a sign that all street users to rotan sreet 16. ..COULDN&#039;T. (can) enter it \nthat day because one of the residents was having a weeding party. 17. \n.I HAD... (have) to turn my car to pasadena street and I was trapped in a \ntrafic jam half an hour. it 18. .WAS... (be) a nuisance. I ..REACHED... (reach) \nhome late in the evening. I think that streets 20...ARE.. (be) \u00a0for public \nuse. it should not be use for private use. if you 21. WILL HOLD....(hold) a \nweeding party, you should rent a weeding hall or a meeting hall in the \nnear sub district. streets 22 .ARE... (be) for trafic, it \u00a023. IS.... (be) \nnot for private party.</span></span>\n            </span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-soal-soal-persuading-195",
            "question": "Contoh soal soal persuading",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Why don\u2019t you\ntry our special drink bandrek to warm up your body?\n\n\n\n\n<br><span>\nIf I were you, I\nwould \u2026 ?</span>\n<span>\n\u00a0I\u2019m sure you are\non the right track.?</span>\n\n\n<br><span>\n\u00a0<span>I bet you could\ndo it.?</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-jelaskan-cara-menggunakan-linking-verb-272",
            "question": "Tolong jelaskan cara menggunakan LINKING VERB",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "penggunaan Linking verbs berfungsi sebagai kata (kerja) penghubung antara subjek dengan keterangannya.<br>example: The kids\u00a0<strong>act</strong> foolish.<br><br><strong>Act</strong> dalam kalimat itu adalah contoh linking verb.<br><br>semoga bisa membantu ^_^,,,<br>maaf kalau ada yang salah ^_^,,,",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>penggunaan Linking verbs berfungsi sebagai kata (kerja) penghubung antara subjek dengan keterangannya.<br>example: The kids\u00a0act foolish.</span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "their-motivationimprove-if-they-858",
            "question": "Their motivation...............(improve) if they..........................(kick) a goal during the first half",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "their motivation increases when the kick goal during the first half<br><br>kalau salah gak apa-apa ya<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-jelasin-secara-singkat-conditional-sntence-type-3-trims-835",
            "question": "Tolong jelasin secara singkat \"Conditional Sntence\" Type 3 ,trims..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kalimat pengandaian untuk masa lalu dimana kalimatnya bertentangan<br>main clouse( s+ would/should+have+v3) if clouse( if+s+had+v3) jika if clouse tidak mempunyai kata kerja maka ditambah have been<br>contoh : he could have if his computer had not broken down",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Suatu kalimat pengandainya yang bertentangan dengan masa lalu.<br>Contohnya :<br>If you had said your guilty, I would have forgiven you<br>If + past perfect, S + would/should + have + past participle",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bahasa-inggrisnya-mengacak-acak-rambutnya-667",
            "question": "Apa Bahasa Inggrisnya mengacak-acak rambutnya?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "bahasa inggris nya adalah mess her/his hair",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Ruffled/Mess his/her hair<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-describe-dengan-tema-my-beloved-home-386",
            "question": "Tolong describe dengan tema \"my beloved home\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "My beloved home<br><br>It is located in the central park. My home is the sweetest home on my complex. It has green roof which is made from special clay. Therefore it is always shining when the sun light rise in the morning.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "my home.. my everything.. even\u00a0my home not as huge the president home or a museums.. even my home don&#039;t as rich as the businessman home.. i love my home.. because my home protect me from the light of the sun , from the extreme weather , from the cold of the rain.. but i still love my home..home sweet home.. you&#039;re my protecter from childhood.. how bad you&#039;re you still my home... i called it my beloved home",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-the-word-darling-is-derived-from-an-old-english-term-meaning-251",
            "question": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old english term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".    2. IBM is has laid of 20 percent of their workforce with a signature on a single piece of paper.\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6\r\na. Find out the error option.\r\nb. Explain why it is wrong\r\n\r\nmohon bantuannya yaa..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old English term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".<br>Positive Meaning : It&#039;s a person that we concern as lovely and lovable, therefore we prioritize this darling as the first priority.<br>Negative : Since the word darling means favorite minion, it also trigger the feeling of possessiveness, that sometime it has negative effect on their freedom and privacy.\u00a0<br><br><span>2.\u00a0</span><u>IBM</u><span>\u00a0is\u00a0</span><u>has</u><span>\u00a0laid of\u00a0</span><u>20 percent</u><span>\u00a0of\u00a0</span><u>their</u>\u00a0<u>workforce</u><span>\u00a0with a signature on a\u00a0</span><u>single</u><span>\u00a0piece of paper.</span><br>\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6<br>a. Find out the error option.<br><br>number 2 - &gt; should be<br>IBM has laid without &#039;is&#039;\u00a0<br>b. Explain why it is wrong<br>if we use Is, then it will have pasive meaning, which means that IBM get bankrupt due to their worker\u00a0<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "5-kalimat-verbal-dalam-bahasa-inggris-610",
            "question": "5\u00a0kalimat verbal dalam\u00a0bahasa inggris?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "We play football every morning<br>I go to the market every sunday<br>She plays soccer with Ella<br>He goes to the library<br>She buys some books in the store<br>Semoga Membantu<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "terdiri-dari-apa-sajakah-causative-have-itu-798",
            "question": "Terdiri dari apa sajakah causative have itu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Causative verb menunjukkan bahwa seseorang/sesuatu secara tidak langsung bertanggung jawab terhadap sebuah tindakan. Subjek tidak melakukan tindakan itu sendiri, tetapi justru menyebabkan seseorang/sesuatu yang lain melakukannya. Contoh:<br>- Yesterday I had my hair cut.<br>Pembicara pada kalimat diatas tidak memotong sendiri rambutnya, tetapi justru membuat orang lain melakukannya \u2013 Saya \u201cmenyebabkan\u201d mereka memotong rambut saya.<br>Have<br>Have merupakan causative verb yang umum. Ketimbang melakukan sesuatu dengan diri kita sendiri, kita \u201cmenyuruh\u201d orang yang lain untuk melakukannya. Bentuknya sebagai berikut:<br>Kata kerja \u201cto have\u201d + objek + past participle (verb 3). Contoh:<br>- I had my jacket cleaned yesterday.<br>- Did you have your computer fixed?<br>Terkadang kita menggunakan have sebagai causative verb ketika kita ingin melakukan tindakan oleh diri kita sendiri. Contoh:<br>- When will the report be ready? I\u2019ll do it by tomorrow morning. &gt;&gt;<br>- When will the report be ready? I\u2019ll have it done by tomorrow morning.<br>Dengan menggunakan causative, kalimat ke-dua diatas mengalihkan perhatian dari pelaku tindakan, dan lebih memberikan perhatian kepada tindakan yang sedang dilakukan. Ini kedengaran sopan dan profesional.<br>Get<br>Get sering digunakan ketimbang have. Contoh:<br>\u2022\tI got my computer fixed \u2013 I had my computer fixed. Kedua kalimat ini maknanya sama.<br>\u2022\tI got my jacket cleaned. \u2013 I had my jacket cleaned. Kedua kalimat ini maknanya sama.<br>Causative verbs sering digunakan bersama dengan pengalaman-pengalaman negatif. Pada situasi-situasi ini lebih umum menggunakan have. Contoh:<br>\u2022\tI had my wallet stolen. (Saya sebenarnya tidak menyebabkan dompet saya dicuri \u2013 seseorang mencuri dompet saya dariku)<br><span>\u2022\tShe had her window smashed.<br><br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}